The world's not going to save itself.
Men in Black: International is a comedy, science
fiction, action film directed by F. Gary Gray.
The Men in Black have always protected the Earth from the scum of the universe.
In this new adventure, they tackle their biggest, most global threat
to date: a mole in the Men in Black organization.
Henry / Agent H, played by Chris Hemsworth.
Molly Wright / Agent M, played by Tessa Thompson.
Riza Stavros, played by Rebecca Ferguson.
Pawny (voice), played by Kumail Nanjiani.
Agent C, played by Rafe Spall.
Alien Twin #1, played by Laurent Bourgeois.
Men in Black: International (stylized as MIB: International in promotional material)
is a 2019 American science fiction action-comedy film directed by F.
Gary Gray and written by Art Marcum and Matt Holloway.
It is the fourth in the Men in Black film series, based on The Men in Black
comic book series, in turn based on the conspiracy theory.
It is set in the same universe as the previous films, but is the first in
the series to feature neither Will Smith nor Tommy Lee Jones.
It stars Chris Hemsworth, Tessa Thompson, Kumail Nanjiani,
Rebecca Ferguson, Rafe Spall, and Liam Neeson.
Emma Thompson reprises her role from the third film, while Tim Blaney
returns to voice Frank the Pug from the first two installments.
The film follows the Men in Black taking on its
biggest threat: a mole in the agency.
Talks of a fourth Men in Black film began after the
release of Men in Black 3 in 2012.
In February 2018, Hemsworth signed on to lead a spin-off, Gray was hired to
direct, and Thompson joined the cast the following month.
Filming took place in New York City, Morocco, Italy
and London from July to October 2018.
Danny Elfman, who had scored the previous three installments,
returned to compose the reboot with Chris Bacon.
The film was marred by significant production strife between producer Walter F.
Parkes and director Gray during the production.
Men in Black: International premiered in New York City on June 11, 2019,
followed by a nationwide theatrical release three days later.
The film received generally negative reviews from critics, who criticized the action and plot, and was a
financial disappointment, grossing $253.9 million worldwide against a $94–110 million production budget.
The film explores themes of london, england, paris, france,
secret organization, sahara desert, based on comic.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.